Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (VADP); Records apap304
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administration, 1984-2023; 1; 2.2 cubic ft.; 3.39 GB
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2009 November 19
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2009 December 17
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2009 December 17
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2010 January 26
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2010 February 22
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2010 March 23
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2010 May 26
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2010 July 6
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2010 July 6
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2010 July 6
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2010 August 11
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2010 August 11
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2010 October 27
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2010 October 27
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2011 January 11
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2011 January 11
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2011 February 28
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2011 April 26
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2011 June 21
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2011 August 1
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2011 September 19
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2011 December 7
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2012 January 16
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2012 April 25
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2012 September 14-2015 September 15; 2012 September 15; 2012 November 16
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2012 October 16
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2012 November 12
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2012 December 17
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2013 January 21
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2013 February 19
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2013 March 23
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2013 April 25
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2013 June 6
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2013 July 30
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2013 August 13
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2013 August 26
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2013 September 24
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2013 November 6
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2013 December 10
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2014 January 20
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2014 March 26
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2014 May 15
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, 2014 November 12; 2014 December 8
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, Addendum, 2014 March 26
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, Draft, 2011 February 28
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, Draft, 2011 April 26
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, Draft, 2011 June 21
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, Draft, 2011 December 7
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, Draft, 2012 November 12
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, Draft, 2012 December 17
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, Draft, 2013 February 19
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, Draft, 2011 August 1
  - VADP Board Meeting Minutes, including financial numbers, 2012 January 16
  - VADP Board Member Agreement, Unsigned, Undated
  - VADP Board of Directors, 2011 January 20
  - VADP Board of Directors, 2011 January 20; 2015 January 12
  - VADP Board of Directors, 2014
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, 2015 April 3
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, 2017 September 22; 2018 August 31
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, 2020 January 20
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2015 April 27
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2015 April 27
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2015 May 1
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2015 June 16
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2015 September 8
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2015 December 3
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2016 June 1
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2016 September 12
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2016 September 28
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2017 January 13
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2017 February 2
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2017 September 1
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2017 September 22
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2018 March 13
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2018 September 12
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2018 September 24
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2019 January 22
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2019 March 4
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2019 September 1
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2019 September 16
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2020 March 2
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2020 March 2
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2020 September 1
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2020 September 24
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2020 September 28
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2020 November 25
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2021 November 9
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2022 September 1
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2022 September 8
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, 2022 November 23
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Officers, Revised, 2017 September 1
  - VADP Board of Directors Members & Terms of Service, Summary, 2020 January 20
  - VADP Board Retreat Action Plan, 2014; 2014 November 11
  - VADP Board Retreat Action Plan, 2014; 2014 December 9
  - VADP Board Retreat Agenda, 2012 September 14-2012 September 15; 2012 August 19
  - VADP Board Survey on VADP Future, Results, 2021 April 7
  - VADP Board Survey on VADP Future, Results Final, 2021 April 7
  - VADP Budget Draft, 2017; 2018 July 27
  - VADP Budget Narrative, 2017
  - VADP Budget Projection for Board Meeting, 2013 December 10
  - VADP Budget Projection for Board Meeting, 2014 March 11
  - VADP Budget Projection for Board Meeting, 2014 March 26
  - VADP Budget Projection, 6 Months, 2014 January 20
  - VADP By-Laws, Adopted 2007, 2017 September 20
  - VADP Calendar of Events, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - VADP Calendar with Notes, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - VADP Campaign for Organization Campaign Participation, 2008 October 29; 2008 October 30
  - VADP Check from Tides Foundation for Website Redesign, 2015 June 12; 2015 June 18
  - VADP Church Donation Report, 2008-2011; 2011 April 26
  - VADP Completed Sign Up Sheet, 2013 November 26
  - VADP Conference, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - VADP Conference, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - VADP Conflict of Interest Agreement, Signed by Mary Atwell, 2014 January 20; 2014 January 21
  - VADP Conflict of Interest Agreement, Signed by Meghan Shapiro, 2014 January 21
  - VADP Conflict of Interest Policy, Signed Elizabeth Panilaitis, 2014 January 21; 2014 February 7
  - VADP Cover Letter from Tides Foundation for Website Redesign, 2015 June 12; 2015 June 18
  - VADP Database Records to be Deleted, 2018 April; 2018 April 17
  - VADP Death Penalty Fact Sheet, 2011; 2011 September 17
  - VADP Death Penalty Fact Sheet, 2012; 2012 September 19
  - VADP Death Penalty Fact Sheet, 2013 June 11
  - VADP Director's Report, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - VADP Donation Return Envelope Design, 2018 February 15
  - VADP Donor Faith Communities Award Luncheon Invitation, 2015 August 7
  - VADP Donor Level Report of $500 or More, 1980-2011; 2011 May 3; 2011 April 30
  - VADP Donor Level Report-Individuals, 2011; 2011 April 30
  - VADP Donor Levels Document, 2009 May 1
  - VADP Donors listed from largest to smallest donations, 2010
  - VADP Donors listed from largest to smallest donations, 2011; 2012 September 11
  - VADP Donors listed from largest to smallest donations, 2012; 2012 September 19
  - VADP Draft Staff meeting Notes, with Notes from Steve and Michael, 2011 April 1
  - VADP End of the Year Statement of Financial Position, 2021; 2021 June 22; 2022 January 11
  - VADP Engagement Tool, Suddes Group- Draft, 2016 October 21
  - VADP Equal Justice and Fair Play Press Release, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - VADP Executive Board Biographies, Undated
  - VADP Executive Board, 2006; 2007 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - VADP Executive Board Activities Committee, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - VADP Executive Board Finance Committee, 2004; 2005 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - VADP Executive Board Meeting, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - VADP Executive Board Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - VADP Executive Director Job Advert, 2014 November 2
  - VADP Faith Members, 2015-2023 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - VADP Fast and Vigil, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - VADP Finances- Balance Sheet for Tides Foundation, 2013 December 31; 2013; 2015 January 19
  - VADP Finances- Budget Sheet for Tides Foundation, 2014; 2015 January 19
  - VADP Financial Balance for Board Meeting, 2012 April 25
  - VADP Financial Balance for Board Meeting, 2012 October 16
  - VADP Financial Balance for Board Meeting, 2012 November 12
  - VADP Financial Balance for Board Meeting, 2012 December 17
  - VADP Financial Balance for Board Meeting, 2013 January 21
  - VADP Financial Balance for Board Meeting, 2013 March 23
  - VADP Financial Balance for Board Meeting, 2013 April 25
  - VADP Financial Balance for Board Meeting, 2013 June 6
  - VADP Financial Balance for Board Meeting, 2014 November 12
  - VADP Financial Balance for Board Meeting, 2014 December 9
  - VADP Financial Summary for Board Meeting, 2011 February 28
  - VADP Financial Summary for Board Meeting, 2011 April 26
  - VADP Financial Summary for Board Meeting, 2011 June 21
  - VADP Financial Summary for Board Meeting, 2011 August 1
  - VADP Financial Summary for Board Meeting, 2011 September 19
  - VADP Financial Summary for Board Meeting, 2011 December 7
  - VADP Financial Summary for Board Meeting, 2012 April 25
  - VADP Financial Summary, Electronic Signature, 2020 April 17
  - VADP Form 8868 Application for Extension of Time To File an Exempt Organization Return, 2011; 2011 August 15
  - VADP Fundraising Subcommittee Proposal, 2012 September; 2012 September 4
  - VADP Handouts, Undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - VADP Income & Expense Statement, 2020; 2021 January 6
  - VADP Income and Expense Report for Bon Secours Sisters Ministry Fund, 2016 July; 2016 July 18
  - VADP Income and Expense Statement Budget vs. Actual, 2018; 2018 June 30; 2018 July 27
  - VADP Income for Tide Grant, 2013; 2013-2014; 2014 August 7
  - VADP In-Person Board Meeting Agenda, 2013 March 23
  - VADP In-Person Board Meeting Agenda, Draft, 2013 March 23
  - VADP Interim Strategic Planning Meeting Notes, 2008 October 1
  - VADP Invitations for 25th Anniversary Luncheon, 2016; 2016 July 28
  - VADP Invitations for 26th Anniversary Luncheon, 2017; 2017 August 14
  - VADP IRS 501 (c)(3) Letter, 2016 August 4; 2014 August 12
  - VADP IRS 501 (c)(3) Letter, 2017 August 4
  - VADP IRS Determination Letters, 2008 December 2; 2014 January 30
  - VADP IRS Determination Letters- Addendum, 2014 August 12
  - VADP IRS Form 990, 2018; 2019 March 17
  - VADP IRS Form 990, 2019; 2020 March 12
  - VADP IRS Form 990, 2020; 2021 March 15
  - VADP IRS Form 990, 2021; 2022 January 11
  - VADP IRS Form 990, 2022; 2023 March 15
  - VADP IRS Form 990 for 2017, 2018 July 27
  - VADP IRS Form 990 for 2018, 2019 August 20
  - VADP IRS Penalty Letter, 2008 December 31
  - VADP IRS Tax Exempt Letter, 2014 August 12
  - VADP IRS Tax Exempt Letter, 2014 August 12; 2019 August 20
  - VADP IRS Tax-Exempt Letter for Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Application, 2016 July; 2014 August 12
  - VADP Juvenile Death Penalty Survey, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - VADP Large Donors Sheet, 2011
  - VADP Letter of Appreciation to Jon Sheldon, 2011 August 3
  - VADP List of Large Donors, 2012
  - VADP-Lori Baux 2009 Year End Report, 2008 September 26
  - VADP- Lori Baux VADP Legislative Advocacy Document, 2010 April 30; 2011 March 16
  - VADP Luncheon Catering Teatime Proposal, 2018 September 17; 2018 November 29
  - VADP Major Donor Level, 2011; 2007 October 9
  - VADP Major Donor Level Report- by date, 2011; 2011 April 30
  - VADP Major Donor Level Report- dates and location, 2011; 2011 April 30
  - VADP Major Donor List for Awards Luncheon Invitation, 2015 August 5
  - VADP Major Donor List for Awards Luncheon Invitation, 2015 September 3
  - VADP Major Donors- Detailed History, 2011 May 5; 2011 April 30
  - VADP Major Donors Report, 2009-2010; 2011 May 5
  - VADP March Meeting, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - VADP Meeting Minutes, 2007 September 26
  - VADP Meeting Minutes, 2007 November 17
  - VADP Meeting Minutes, 2007 November 28
  - VADP Meeting Minutes, 2007 December 5
  - VADP Meeting Minutes, 2007 December 12
  - VADP Meeting Minutes, 2008 January 28
  - VADP Meeting Minutes, 2008 February 11
  - VADP Meeting Minutes, 2008 February 27
  - VADP Meeting Minutes, 2008 April 9
  - VADP Meeting Minutes, 2008 June 4
  - VADP Meeting Minutes, 2008 July 28
  - VADP Meeting Minutes, 2009 October 9
  - VADP Meeting Minutes, 2009 October 24
  - VADP Meeting Notes, 2008 January 15
  - VADP Meetings, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - VADP Members Who Donate to the Senate, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - VADP Narrative for 2014 Tides Foundation Application, 2015 January 19
  - VADP New Logo Image, Square, 2012 February; 2012 October 19
  - VADP Newsletter, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - VADP Newsletter, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - VADP Organization/Project Budget Template, 2020; 2019 August 20
  - VADP Part IX Financial Data 501c3, Form 1023 Application for Recognition of Exemption, Horizontal Chart, 2013 December 24
  - VADP Part IX Financial Data 501c3, Form 1023 Application for Recognition of Exemption, Vertical Chart, 2013 December 24
  - VADP Past Board Members, 2007 October 3; 2001-2009
  - VADP Progress Report on 2017 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Grant, 2018 July 31; 2018 July 27
  - VADP Progresss Report for May Strategic Planning, 2009 May 1; 2008 September-2009 May
  - VADP Projected Budget, 2006; 2008 February 19
  - VADP Proposed Budget including 2010, 2011; 2011 April 28
  - VADP Reception Catering Teatime Proposal, 2018 September 17
  - VADP Reception CAtering Teatime Proposal, Signed, 2018 September 26
  - VADP Reception Certificate of Liability Insurance, 2018 October 1
  - VADP Reception Insurance Application, 2018 October 19
  - VADP Reception Insurance Info, 2018 October 19; 2018 October 14-2018 October 25
  - VADP Report for Grant Number TFR08-02701, 2009-2010; 2008 November 5
  - VADP Short Form Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax, 2007 November 15
  - VADP Short Form Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax, 2008 August 4
  - VADP Sign Up Sheet, 2011 September 16
  - VADP Sign-Up Sheet, 2013; 2013 June 11
  - VADP Snapshot Draft, 2011 April 30; 2015 January 12
  - VADP Snapshot Fall 2012, 2012 September 13
  - "VADP Snapshot" PDF Slide Deck, 2011 May
  - VADP Snapshot Spring 2011 Powerpoint, 2011 May 5
  - VADP Snapshot Spring 2011 Powerpoint, Final, 2011 May 6
  - VADP Snapshot Spring 2011 Powerpoint, New, 2011 May 6
  - "VADP Snapshot" Presentation, 2011 May
  - VADP Snapshot Template, 2011 March 25
  - VADP Snapshot Template, Spring 2011, 2011 May 5
  - VADP Snapshot, Template, 2015 January; 2015 January 14
  - VADP Spring Fundraiser Draft Letter, 2011 April; 2011 May 18
  - VADP Statement of Finanacial Income and Expense, 2017 January 1-2017 December 31; 2018 January 8
  - VADP Statement of Financial Income and Expense, 2019 January-2019 July; 2019 August 13
  - VADP Statement of Financial Income and Position, 2018 January-2018 June; 2018 July 3; 2018 June 30
  - VADP Statement of Financial Position, 2018; 2018 June 30; 2018 July 3; 2018 July 27
  - VADP Statement of Financial Position, 2019 July 31; 2019 August 13
  - VADP Straegic Planning Minutes, 2008 May 16
  - VADP Strategic Planning Meeting, 2009 April 27
  - VADP Strategic Planning Meeting Agenda, 2009 May 1; 2009 May 2; 2009 April 23
  - VADP Strategic Planning Meeting Agenda, with Allies, 2009 May 2; 2009 April 23
  - VADP Strategic Planning Meeting Facilitator's Agenda, 2009 May 1; 2009 May 2; 2009 April 23
  - VADP Strategic Planning Meeting Minutes, 2009 May 7-2009 May 8; 2010 May; 2010 June 2
  - VADP Strategic Planning Meeting Minutes, 2009 May 7-2009 May 8; 2011 March 16
  - VADP Strategic Planning Meeting Minutes, 2010 May 7
  - VADP Strategic Planning Meeting Notes, 2008 September 26
  - VADP Strategic Planning Meeting Notes, 2009 September 8; 2009 September 26; 2009 May 1
  - VADP Strategy Document for 2020, 2016 January 7
  - VADP Strategy Document for 2020 Revised, 2016 February 27
  - VADP Strategy Document for 2020, Suddes Group Template Draft, 2016 January 11
  - VADP Strategy Document for 2020, Suddes Group Template Draft, Revised, 2016 January 26
  - VADP Strategy Document for Major Donors, 2015 December 1
  - VADP Strategy Document for Major Donors, Revised, 2015 December 7
  - VADP Strategy Document for Major Donors, Second Revision, 2015 December 14
  - VADP Strategy Document for Majors Donors, Revised, 2018 May 29
  - VADP Suddes Group Engagement Tool, 2016 December 2
  - VADP Suddes Group Engagement Tool, 2017 October 3
  - VADP Suddes Group Engagement Tool, 2019 April 16
  - VADP Tax Extentsion, 2010
  - VADP Tax Return, 2010
  - "VADP Thirty History in Photos" Graphic, 2021 November 23
  - VADP, Thirty Years of History in Photographs- Powerpoint, 2021 August 19
  - VADP, Thirty Years of History in Photographs, Revised- Powerpoint, 2021 August 24
  - VADP, Thirty Years of History in Photographs, Second Revision- Powerpoint, 2021 November 16
  - VADP, Thirty Years of History in Photographs, Second Revision- Video, 2021 November 16
  - VADP Tides Foundation Application Narrative & Bios, 2010
  - VADP, Tides Foundation Budget Template for Death Penalty Mobilization Fund, 2014; 2013-2014
  - VADP Tides Foundation Cover Sheet, 2015 July 27; 2015 November 1
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- 2014 IRS Form 990, 2015 July 27
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- 2015 Grants Committed Chart, 2015 July 27
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- Bios of Key Individuals, 2016 August 4
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- Bios of Key Individuals, 2017 August 4
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- Budget Template, 2016 August 4; 2017
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- Budget Template, 2017 August 4
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- Budget Template, Revised, 2015 July 30; 2015 November 1-2016 October 31
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- Budget Template, Revised, 2015 July 30
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- IRS Letter, 2015 July 27; 2014 August 12
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- Proposal Narrative, 2016 August 4
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- Proposal Narrative, 2017 August 4
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- Statement of Financial Income and Expense, 2016 August 4; 2016 January 3; 2015
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- Statement of Financial Income and Expense, 2017 August 4
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- Statement of Financial Position, 2017 August 4
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund-Bios of Key Individuals, 2015 July 27
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund-Budget Template, 2015 July 27; 2015 November 1-2016 October 31
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund-Finances/Balance Sheet, 2015 July 27; 2014 December 31
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund-Profit and Loss Budget vs. Actual, 2015 July 27; 2015 January-2015 June
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund-Profit and Loss Statement, 2015 July 27; 2014
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund-Proposal Narrative, 2015 July 27
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund-Year to Date Income and Expense Report, 2016 August 4; 2016 July
  - VADP Tides Foundation Death Penalty Mobilization Fund-Year to Date Income and Expense Report, 2017 August 4
  - VADP Tides Foundation Final Grant Report, Capacity Building Grant, 2015 November 23; 2015 November 18
  - VADP Tides Foundation Final Grant Report, Death Penalty Mobilization Fund, 2015 March 30
  - VADP Tides Foundation Final Grant Report, Death Penalty Mobilization Fund, 2015 October 30
  - VADP Tides Foundation Final Grant Report, Death Penalty Mobilization Fund, 2016 October 24
  - VADP Tides Foundation Final Grant Report, Death Penalty Mobilization Fund, 2017 July 13
  - VADP Tides Foundation Grant Report, Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Grant, 2017; 2018 July 31
  - VADP Tides Foundation Interim Grant Report, Advocacy Grant Fund, 2015 March 30
  - VADP Tides Foundation Interim Grant Report, Advocacy Grant Fund, 2015 October 30
  - VADP Tides Foundation Interim Grant Report, Death Penalty Mobilization Fund, 2015 March 30
  - VADP Tides Foundation Interim Grant Report, Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- Balance Sheet, 2015 December 31; 2016 January 3; 2016 March 31
  - VADP Tides Foundation Interim Grant Report, Death Penalty Mobilization Fund- Financial Statement, 2015; 2016 January 3
  - VADP, Tides Foundation Organizational Summary Sheet, 2014; 2013-2014; 2015 January 19
  - VADP Tides Foundation Organizational Summary Sheet, 2016 August 4
  - VADP Tides Foundation Organizational Summary Sheet, 2017 August 4
  - VADP Tides Foundation with Strategic Vision, 2010
  - VADP Tides Grants VADP Budget, 2014; 2014 August 8
  - VADP Tracking Sheet, Undated
  - VADP Web Site, Google Analytics 2017 Data by Month, 2018 February 6
  - VADP Year End Finances, 2010
  - VADP Year End Finances and Proposed 2012 Budget, 2011; 2012 February 8
  - VADP Year in Review, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - VADP Year to Date Finances, 2014 May 15
  - VAMC Meeting, 2006-2007; Undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - VAMC Minutes, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - VAMC Tides Grant, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Video Project Agreement with Hunter Brumfield, 2021 November 19
  - Video Project Invoice (1 of 2), 2021 August 26
  - Vigil Permit, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Virginia Association Against the Death Penalty (VAADP), 1985; 1986; 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Virginia Coalition on Jails and Prisons, 1984; 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Death Penalty Editorial Cartoon (labeled 1982), 1982 August 11; 2021 August 3
  - Virginia Death Sentences Over Time Graphic, 2012; 2013 May 13
  - Virginia General Assembly Questionnaire, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Virginia General Assembly Questionnaire, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Heroes of Death Penalty Abolition, 2020 August 25
  - Virginia Lynching Website Screenshot, 2017 October 10
  - Virginia Moratorium Groups, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Newspapers Stance on the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Organizing 2013 Exempt Organization Form 990 Return, 2014 May 23
  - Virginia Organizing Financial Statements for VADP for Tides Foundation Application, 2012-2013; 2014; 2015 January 19
  - Virginia Organizing IRS Form 990 for 2013, 2014 August 7; 2014 May 23
  - Virginia People of Faith Meeting, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 6)